下面我们讲讲Loaders。Loaders是一个很棒的东西。
Let's talk about Loaders. Loaders are awesome. They were
在Honeycomb中被引入开发框架，然而那时仅仅是兼容库的一部分。
introduced in Honeycomb, but are available as part of the
所以你可以利用兼容库
support library. So you can take advantage of them
在旧版本的系统中使用该特性。
when supporting earlier platform releases. Loaders are essentially the best
Loaders对于Activity或Fragment中的异步数据读取来说基本上是最好的实现方法。
practice implementation for asynchronous data loading within an activity
所以当你创建了一个Loader，它会创建
or fragment. So when you create a Loader, it creates
一个asyncTask对象在后台读取数据。
an async task to load data on the background thread.
当初始化数据读取完成后，它会在UI线程中进行同步,
It then syncs with the UI thread when the initial
也可以通过它来监听正在处理的数据
loading is complete, and can be set up to monitor
将数据的更新同步到UI线程
the underlying data, and deliver any updates to the UI
之前你所做的那些工作，
thread as well. Best still, all that work you did
添加ContentProvider到你的数据库，
adding a content provider to your database pays off right
在这里可以通过CursorLoader来发挥作用了。CursorLoader
now, with the cursor loader. The cursor loader is an
是AsyncTaskLoader（异步任务读取）的实现类，它专门用于处理对Content Provider的请求，
implementation of the async task loader, specifically designed to query
通过返回Cursor对象来实现数据读取。你可以将
content providers, and return a cursor, which you can then
该Cursor与UI进行线程绑定。它会随着Content Provider数据的改变
bind directly to a UI. It will automatically update that cursor,
自动更新Cursor。更新操作会机遇底层的数据库进行。
whenever the underlying content provider changes, based on changes
在程序设置发生改变后，
to the underlying database. And it will reconnect to the
CursorLoader会在重新创建时重新连接
last returned cursor after being recreated, along with the
当前Activity中最后返回的Cursor。这意味着
host activity, after a configuration change. That means you won't
你不需要在设备屏幕仅仅被旋转就重新请求数据。
have to requery data, just because the device was
CursorLoader会处理所有的Cursor管理和
rotated. So the cursor loader handles all of your cursor
后台线程创建，UI线程同步，以及数据监听。
management and background thread creation, UI thread synchronization, and data
如果你不使用Content Provider，
source monitoring. If you chose not to use content providers,
那么你的选择就少了。但是你仍然可以使用loaders，
you chose poorly. But still, you can take advantage
通过继承AsyncTaskLoader
of loaders, you just need to create your own
来创建你自己的Loader类。
loader by extending async task loader directly. You
关于更多相关内容，你可以参考下面的指导信息。
can find out more in the instructor notes below.